[{"id": 1284, "question": "When looking for love, people may go to some extreme lengths. They might go on blind dates set up by family and friends. They might write personal ad to place in newspapers. Or they might use a computer to help them in their search for a soul mate by joining an online dating service. Some people have even tried to find their perfect match through game shows on television. Many of these TV dating shows, including The Bachelor andWho Wants to Marry Multimillionaire?, have proved to be popular, with millions of viewers watching each week to find out which of the contestants will find true love. Of all these game shows, perhaps the one with the most unexpected ending was Mr. Right, which was shown in England in 2002. On the show, a bachelor, thirty-five-year-old Lance Gerrard-Wright, dated fif...\n\nQ: Why did some of Ulrika's friends feel upset?", "options": ["They didn't agree with the marriage.", "They weren't asked to attend the wedding.", "There weren't enough guests at the wedding.", "They didn't like Lance."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2379, "question": "Tim Welford, aged 33, and Dom Mee, aged 30, both from England, were keen on (=\"like...\" very much) rowing boats. They made a plan to row across the Pacific Ocean from Japan to San Francisco. The name of their rowboat was \"Crackers\". It was about seven meters long. They set out from Japan on May 17,2001. They had rowed nearly 5,500 miles when their boat was hit by a fishing ship on September 17,2001. Luckily they both escaped unharmed, but their boat was badly damaged and they had to abandon( =\" stop)their\" journey. In a radio interview, Dom expressed his disappointment and explained how the accident took place. \"A fishing ship came towards us with nobody on the bridge and ran us down. It all happened so quickly. I managed to dive into the water. Tim felt it would be safer to stay on board....\n\nQ: 44. Which of the following statements is NOT TRUE?", "options": ["Some people on the fishing ship saved them.", "Tim and Dom were going to San Francisco in the rowboat because they had no money to buy airplane tickets.", "Dom dived into the water when the accident happened because he thought it would be dangerous to stay on board.", "Dom told people about their dangerous experience when he was interviewed on the radio."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 630, "question": "In the US and Britain, the slogan around colleges was \"Save water. Shower with a friend.\" Now, Wuhan University has come up with another system for the campus bathhouse. It charges students for the amount of time in a shower. Before entering the bathhouse, students pay for the amount of time they want in the shower with cash or their student ID card. The clock starts ticking the minute the tape is turned on. It pauses when a button is pressed for soap. An integrated circuit (IC) card reader at each tap shows the time. No money, no water. The benefits of the new system can be seen with the old system, which charged 1 Yuan for each person regardless of time in the shower. The university used about 320 tons of water daily under the old system, but only 160 tons now. Many students use the new ...\n\nQ: Since the new system has performed,   _   of water can be saved.", "options": ["a quarter", "one third", "one half", "two thirds"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 841, "question": "Individuality is the particular character, or aggregate (total) of qualities that distinguishes one person or thing from others. Many artists late in the last century were in search of a means to express their individuality. Modern dance was one of the ways some of these people sought to free their creative spirit. At the beginning there was no exacting technique, no foundation from which to build. In later years, trial, error and genius founded the techniques and the principles of the movement. Eventually, innovators even drew from what they considered the dread ballet, but first they had to get rid of all that was academic so that the new could be discovered. The beginnings of modern dance were happening before Isadora Duncan, but she was the first person to bring the new dance to genera...\n\nQ: Which of the following is not mentioned as an area of dance that Duncan worked to change?", "options": ["The stage set.", "The music.", "Costumes.", "Movements."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3213, "question": "Every day is a gift, and if you look forward to spending each day with happiness, wake up every morning with a positive attitude and enjoy a beautiful day! Set up a daily plan for yourself and ensure that you reserve enough time for your homework. Also, don't forget to spare some time for play! Stop being lazy and start participating in your life instead of just watching it pass by. Try to do something fun and constructive every day. _ , write something interesting in your diary, try a new hobby, spend time with your friends, or just watch your favorite show on television, and you will see how every moment of your day unfolds. You'll achieve better results, and ultimately greater success. However, every day will not be the way you want it to be. Some days will be good, while some will be b...\n\nQ: What would be the best title for the passage?", "options": ["How to make the most of your day", "How to lead a happy and satisfying life", "Act now without delay to change your life", "Spare time to focus on daily responsibilities"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3221, "question": "Thomas Brodie-Sangster's cars and action figures weren't just toys. \"They would always be characters, and I would always put on stupid voices,\" says Thomas (Born on 16 May 1990). For him, acting was just a matter of moving childhood games to a set. Maturity and independence came to Thomas early as he started work at ten. After his first audition , he learned about _ . Though hurt and disappointed, he took a part in a tiny, unknown TV film in 2001. No one noticed his performance - no one except screenwriter Richard Curtis. Two years later, he played Sam, a twelve-year-old in love in Curtis's Love Actually. After that hit film, he played actor Colin Firth's son in Nanny McPhee. Firth then joined a film called The Last Legion and supported Thomas for its lead role. As a result, the boy played...\n\nQ: What can be considered as one of the negative aspects of acting according to Thomas?", "options": ["Pressure from the public.", "Long-term working friendship.", "Finding joy in difficulty itself.", "Reading scripts and memorizing lines."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1768, "question": "Dear Cassy, Thanks for reminding me by e-mail that you want to baby-sit our children. In spite of the fact that you are only 15 years old, my wife and I would be willing to consider your application if you can meet a few modest requirements: 1. three letters from teachers who will prove that you have never failed to follow directions perfectly in class and never failed to hand in the homework on time. 2. Submit a note from two doctors which says that you are in perfect health, have never been sick, and will never be sick. 3. Submit a document from your physical education teacher or team coach that proves that you can do each of the following: Run two miles in less than nine minutes, climb an oily rope to a height of twenty feet in thirty seconds while balancing a glass of water on your nos...\n\nQ: Which of the following words can best describe the Smiths?", "options": ["Humorous.", "Patient.", "Honest.", "Kind-hearted."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3267, "question": "If you are ever planning to buy a telescope and want to get yourself involved in astronomy it is always a good idea to know a bit of the sky.Get acquainted with a few constellations so that it will be easier for you to spot the constellations when you are using your telescope. It's a good idea to buy a few magazines on astronomy to help you to get familiar with the constellations in the sky and also read a few reviews on the different types of telescopes in the market.This will help you gather all the information that is out there regarding telescopes and what people have to say about them. It's advisable to go in for a pair of binoculars before you buy your first telescope so that you can get used to spotting constellations before your view of the sky is narrowed down.This will also help ...\n\nQ: Why does the author advise buying a pair of binoculars first?", "options": ["The telescope is too expensive.", "The binoculars are easier to use.", "You may gain plenty of experience in astronomy.", "Your view will be narrow by using a pair of binoculars."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2837, "question": "In the late 1960's, many people in North America turned their attention to environmental problems, and new steel-and-glass skyscrapers were widely criticized. Ecologists pointed out that a forest of tall buildings in a city often overburdens public transportation and parking lots. Skyscrapers are also consumers and wasters of electric power. In one recent year, the addition of 17 million square feet of skyscrapers office space in New York City raised the peak daily demand for electricity by 120,000 kilowatts--enough to supply the entire city of Albany, prefix = st1 /New York, for a day. Glass-walled skyscrapers can be especially wasteful. The heat loss ( or gain) through a wall of half-inch plate glass is more than ten times that through a typical brick wall filled with insulation board. T...\n\nQ: According to the passage, in the late 1960's some residents of Bostonwere concerned with which aspect of skyscrapers?", "options": ["The noise from their construction.", "The high cost of renting an office.", "The harmful effects on the city's grass.", "The removal of trees from building sites."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2507, "question": "No one knows for certain why people dream, but some dreams misht be connected to the mental processes that help us learn. In a recent study, scientists found a connection between nap-time dreams and better memory in people who were learning a new skill. \"I was astonished by this finding,\" Robert Stickgold told Science News. He is a cognitive neuroscientist at Harvard Medical School who worked on the study of-how the brain and nervous system work, and cognitive studies look at how people learn and reason. So a cognitive neuroscientist may study the brain processes that help people learn. In the study, 99 college students between the ages of 18 and 30 each spent an hour on a computer, trying to get through a virtual maze . The maze was difficult, and the study participants had to start in a ...\n\nQ: The purpose of the study attended by 99 college students is to  _  .", "options": ["find the hidden tree in the maze", "test the design of a difficult virtual maze", "train people's memory", "see how dreams and learning are connected"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 825, "question": "There are millions of used cell phones in the world today. Most of them just lay in our houses without any purpose. Every day dozens of new cell phone models appear. Today, you can find what was regarded as a fantasy yesterday in store and you will buy it tomorrow. But what to do with the old phones, which work well enough and not so old? Just get some money! Simply Sellular is buying almost all models of cell phones: LG, Motorola, Siemens, Samsung, Sanyo, Nokia and many other cell phones. Also they accept phones produced in every country, and in every condition. Simply Sellular can offer a good price for your old cell phone in cash. Their mission is giving you a simple way to get money for an old phone, as simple and profitable, as possible. Also they offer a trade-in scheme to get anothe...\n\nQ: The cell phone donated by you is probably   _  .", "options": ["still in use by others", "refurbished and sold again", "collected and on show", "sent to a poorer country"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1190, "question": "Why do men die earlier than women? The latest research makes it known that the reason could be that men's hearts go into rapid decline when they reach middle age. The largest study of the effects of ageing on the heart has found that women's _ may be linked to the fact that their hearts do not lose their pumping power with age. \"We have found that the power of the male heart falls by 20-25 percent between 18 and 70 years of age,\" said the head of the study, David Goldspink of Liverpool John Moores University in the UK. \"Within the heart there are millions of cells that enable it to beat. Between the age of 20 and 70, one-third of those cells die and are not replaced in men,\" said Goldspink. \"This is part of the ageing process.\" What surprises scientists is that the female heart sees very l...\n\nQ: We can know from the passage that   _  .", "options": ["the reason why ageing takes a greater loss on the male heart has been found out", "scientists are on the way to finding out why the male heart loses more of the cells", "the team has done something to prevent the male from suffering the greater loss", "women over 70 could lose more heart cells than those at the age of 20"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 973, "question": "Do you scream on a roller coaster ride? You slowly climb up a steep slope until an almost vertical drop, and then... Ahhhhhhhh! Thrill-seekers like me are in luck because theme parks are pushing the boundaries of technology to create the fastest, tallest, scariest roller coasters the world has ever known. Alton Towers in Britain opened the world's first 14-1oop roller coaster a few months ago, called The Smiler. Over in Abu Dhabi, Ferrari World claims to have the world's fastest one. Ferrari World's Formula Rossa ride sends out passengers from 0-240km/h in just 4. 9 seconds. During this rapid acceleration they experience G-forces only fighter pilots usually feel: Up to 4. 8G. The designer of several rides at Alton Towers, said: \"While we can stand 6-8Gs for very short periods of time, ff w...\n\nQ: The feature of the \"coal-mine-themed\" ride is", "options": ["3Dtechnologies", "indoor rides", "G-forces", "dynamic structures"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2720, "question": "Holiday houses in Mallorca sailing and fishing port - quiet even in summer season. Beautifully situated houses with sights of sea and mountains, yet near to shops and restaurants. Cars and bicycles for hire. Sailing and sports clubs nearby. ITALY IN COMFORT Luxury coach( - carriage) trips of Italy, out of normal holiday season. 21days to visit five Italian cities starting from London 1 st May, 1 st September . The trips are guided by profess or Martin Davis. Head of Italian Studies, London University . See the arts and culture of historic Italy. KIBBUTZ HOLIDAYS IN ISRAEL Working holidays on a kibbutz( co -operative farm) in Israel. All nationalities welcome for one to three months, if prepared to work morning with kibbutz members. Accommodation , food and trips to historic sights all prov...\n\nQ: Harry and Kate and their sons would like  _  .", "options": ["a holiday working on a kibbutz in Israel", "a holiday visiting cities by coach in Italy", "a holiday house in the fishing port in Mallorca", "a holiday hotel on a lovely beach on a Carribean Island"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3173, "question": "My student teaching experience was a wonderful adventure. I had to deal with various discipline and behavior challenges that occurred again and again. The greatest part of it was the relationship I developed with two students. One of the students was named Michael,whom I met when I was working for a kindergarten. Before I became a morning bus assistant, I'd heard that Michael was a challenging student who would always shout, stand up on the bus, make fun of other students, and distract bus driver. So I decided that each morning, when he got on the bus, I'd have Michael sit beside me. At first he didn't like this idea and pouted about it. But soon he settled down, knowing he had no choice. I began to talk to him about little things outside of school life, such as his weekend activities and ...\n\nQ: Which of the following would probably have nothing to do with Tony?", "options": ["He was uninterested in what the teacher was saying.", "He often shouted and stood up to distract the teacher.", "He seemed to stare at nothing and think of nothing.", "He always had a blank sheet of paper on his desk."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 552, "question": "Mo Yan, whose primitive name is Guan Moye, was awarded the Nobel Literature Prize on October 11, 2012.\"Chinese author Mo Yan today won the Nobel Literature Prize for writing that mixes folk tales, history and the contemporary,\" the Swedish Academy announced.\"Through a mixture of fantasy and reality, historical and social perspectives, Mo Yan has created a world reminiscent in its complexity of those in the writing of William Faulkner and Gabriel Garcia Marques, at the same time finding a departure point in old Chinese literature and in oral tradition,\" the Swedish Academy said Mo Yan began writing in 1981 and he has published novels, short stories and essays on various topic, and despite his social criticism is seen in his homeland as one of the foremost contemporary authors, the Nobel Com...\n\nQ: Which novel of Mo Yan won the Mao Dun Literature Prize in 2011?", "options": ["The Mangrove.", "Red Sorghum.", "The Frog.", "History and the contemporary"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1169, "question": "Eva Mozes Kor has good reasons to look down upon Oskar Groning. When she and her twin sister, Miriam, arrived in the Auschwitz death camp, they were met by Josef Mengele and became part of the cruel scientist's experiments. Groning was a junior squad leader at the camp. While Groning could argue he was not directly responsible for procedures carried out on twins,nor for the mass murder of so many others, he played a critical role in the effort to kill Jews. After the war Groning led an ordinary, quiet life until he became alarmed by the rise of Holocaust deniers. He went public with his role and in September 2014 was charged as an accessory to murder. When Groning went on trial in April 2015, Eva Mozes Kor was called as a witness. After her session, she walked straight up to the 93-year-ol...\n\nQ: What is the author's attitude to Eva Mozes Kor's forgiveness?", "options": ["Objective.", "Favorable.", "Doubtful.", "Unclear."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3177, "question": "NOT all math skills are learned in the classroom. Some of them come naturally. Consider the split-second calculations you make when you estimate the number of empty seats on the school bus or the number of cookies in a cookie jar. These estimates can often be done without counting. That's because humans are born with the ability to closely guess the number of items in a group. Researchers call this ability a person's \"number sense\". To see how a person's inborn number sense might be linked to mathematical performance in the classroom, psychologist Justin Halberda and his colleagues from Johns Hopkins University in prefix = st1 /Baltimore,USran some tests. The scientists asked 64 14-year-olds to look at images of yellow and blue dots that flashed on a computer screen for a fraction of a sec...\n\nQ: Which of the following is not true according to the passage?", "options": ["Everyone has an inborn number sense.", "Those who have a strong number sense are sure to do well in math.", "Some of the math skills are inborn.", "Doing a lot of math exercises may help to learn math well."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2352, "question": "Centerville High School Essay Contest \"Write All About It\" Calling All Aspiring Authors--Centerville High School Essay Contest *Rules 1.Students are asked to present essays of 500 to 700 words of their own work. Any essay containing material plagiarized from another source will be disqualified . 2.Manuscripts should be typed double-spaced,with the student's name,address,and grade level on a separate sheet of paper. 3.Essays must be turned in by 4:00 p.m. on November 30.They can be brought to Mrs. Elton in Rom 104 or to Mr. Markham in the school library. *Essay-Writing Tips 1.Catch your readers' interests--Your opening should immediately pull your readers into your essay. Asking a question or starting with an story,quotation,or surprising statement is a good way to do this. 2.Create a pictu...\n\nQ: Thanks are given to the Centerville Writers' Association because it has  _  .", "options": ["offered to judge the contest", "prepared the essay-writing tips", "organized the essay contest", "donated prizes for the contest"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 415, "question": "Grown-ups are often surprised by how well they remember something they learned as children but have never practiced ever since. A man who has not had a chance to go swimming for years can still swim as well as ever when he gets back in the water. He can get on a bicycle after many years and still ride away. He can play catch and hit a ball as well as his son. A mother who has not thought about the words for years can teach her daughter the poem that begins \"Twinkle, twinkle, little star\" or remember the story of Cinderella or Goldilocks and the Three Bears. One explanation is the law of overlearning, which can be stated as follows: Once we have learned something, additional learning trials increase the length of time we will remember it. In childhood we usually continue to practice such sk...\n\nQ: According to the author, being able to use multiplication tables is", "options": ["a result of overlearning", "a special case of cramming", "a skill to deal with math problems", "a basic step towards advanced studies"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 932, "question": "Talk about a real-life hero! Ten-year-old Larry Champagne from St. Louis, Missouri, hit the brake on a runaway school bus. He saved himself and 20 other kids on board from disaster. It all happened in one terrible accident. On the way to school, the bus driver, Ernestine Blackman, suddenly fell ill. Seeing the car was running away, the other kids started to scream, but Larry ran to the front and stopped the bus. \"At first I thought, 'We're going to die,'\" says Larry, \"but after I pressed the brake, I felt safe.\" Larry's speedy reaction made news all over the country. He appeared on TV shows as a hero. The bus company gave Larry a big gift. His school hung a medal of honor around his neck. \"My grandmother always tells me to do what's right,\" says Larry. He thanked his brother, Jerrick, 9, w...\n\nQ: When did Larry finally feel safe?", "options": ["When the kids finally stopped screaming.", "When the police officers arrived.", "Once he pressed the brake, and the bus stopped.", "When the bus driver started driving again."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 641, "question": "The Healthy Habits Survey shows that only about one third of American seniors have correct habits.Here are some findings and expert advice. 1.How many times did you brush your teeth yesterday? *Finding:A full 33% of seniors brush their teeth only once a day. *Step:Remove the 300 types of bacteria in your mouth each morning with a batteryoperated toothbrush.Brush gently for 2 minutes,at least twice a day. 2.How many times did you wash your hands or bathe yesterday? *Finding:Seniors,on average,bathe fewer than 3 days a week.And nearly 30%wash their hands only 4 times a day-half of the number doctors recommend. *Step:We touch our faces around 3,000 times a day-often inviting germs to enter our mouth,nose,and eyes.Use toilet paper to avoid touching the door handle.And,most important,wash your ...\n\nQ: Which of the following is true according to the text?", "options": ["We should keep from touching our faces.", "There are less than 300 types of bacteria in the mouth.", "A kitchen sponge can carry more germs than a toilet.", "We should wash our hands before touching a door handle."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2560, "question": "You may have heard of the book Moby Dick(<<>> ), written by the American author Herman Melville. You may also know that Moby Dick is considered one of the greatest novels ever written. However, it might surprise you to find out Herman Melville was not always a highly regarded author. Melville's first two novels, Typee and Omoo, were widely read and financially successfully. They were both exciting tales of adventures at sea and experiences with people in foreign lands. Melville became quite famous. However, upon the publication of his third book, Mardi, Melville's popularity began to weaken. He was no longer interested in telling tales of pure adventure, and his writing took on a style that alienated the general reading public of his time. Melville published Moby Dick in October of 1851. i...\n\nQ: What is the text mainly about?", "options": ["The main works of Melville.", "The skills in Melville's writing.", "The ups and downs of Melville.", "The reason for Melville's failure."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2959, "question": "Hunters in Mississippi broke a state record for the heaviest alligator ever killed, kicking off the hunting season with two big catches. Dustin Bockman of Wisconsin and two hunting friends caught the 727-pound 13-foot-long beast on Sunday, beating last year's record-setter by 26 pounds, according to the state's Department of Wildlife, Fisheries and Parks. \"We're going to cook it for sure.\" he told Gulf Live. \"There's plenty for me and everybody else.\" He and his team of hunters followed the huge creature for 12 hours until they could get close enough to shoot him with a crossbow. \"He would go to the bottom and sit like a piece of wood. You could do anything with him,\" Bockman said. The hunters then had to figure out how to drag the beast's dead body into their boat. It look four hours of p...\n\nQ: Which of the following is true about Dustin Bockman?", "options": ["He is a Mississippian.", "He is a first-time hunter.", "He will share out the alligator meat.", "He fought the alligator for 12 hours."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2992, "question": "Almost 70 percent of Chinese middle school students have serious problems with their parents, the Beijing Morning Post quoted a survey as saying. The survey showed 6.62 percent of the surveyed students are afraid of their parents while 13.13 percent of them dislike their parents and 56.28 percent were extremely disgusted with or even hate their parents. Only 4.75 percent of the young people surveyed said they like their parents. The recently conducted survey among 3,000 middle school students in a Beijing district asked questions about their attitude toward their parents and family education, the paper said. For many families, conflict between parents and children center on the student's school grades, their weight and their friends. The survey showed that parental influence over children ...\n\nQ: How many young people surveyed said they like their parents?", "options": ["39390.", "19860.", "14250", "168840"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 970, "question": "You have heard of Webster Toys. Webster's have made good, safe, interesting toys for more than a hundred years. Now we sell them, and children play with them, in countries fromprefix = st1 /New ZealandtoNorway, and fromJapantoBrazil. We are looking for someone to sell our toys in the Far East. He (or she) will be between the ages of thirty and forty. He will already have some years of selling in world markets behind him. He will speak good English, and at least one other language of the Far East. The person we are looking for will live inSingapore, and work in our office there, but he will travel for up to six months in any one year. He will know the Far East quite well already. He will know how to sell in old markets and where to find new ones. He will understand money and make more than ...\n\nQ: The person will speak   _  .", "options": ["English and only one other language", "English or any other language", "English or any other Far Eastern language", "English and a Far Eastern language"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2122, "question": "The worst days of any summer are the rainy ones. We spend all year looking forward to nice weather and long, hot days. In winter, with its cloudy days and bitter cold, we dream of those days at the beach, lying on the sand and enjoying the bright and burning sun. And then, summer comes, and it rains. As a child, I would wake up to rainy summer days and come close to crying. It wasn't fair. We suffered through months of school and experienced bad weather for those short ten weeks of freedom. On those rainy summer days, I had nothing fun to do and could only sit inside, staring out at the rain like a bird in a cage. I was an only child, so there was no one else to play with. My father worked from home, so I was not truly alone, but he could not actively play with me since he was at work. It ...\n\nQ: We can learn from the passage that the author   _  .", "options": ["could enjoy the brilliant sun in winter", "preferred reading to playing outside", "had no brothers or sisters", "was often left alone at home"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2134, "question": "Bruce Jun Fan Lee was born in the hour of the Dragon, between 6 and 8 a.m., in the \"Year of the Dragon\" on November 27, 1940 at the Jackson Street Hospital in San Francisco's Chinatown. Today, a plaque in the hospital's entry remembers the place of his birth. Bruce's birth, in the hour and the year of Dragon, is a powerful symbol in Chinese astrology . It would be a strong indication of the powerful life that was to be lived by Bruce Lee and the explosive influence his life would have on countless others. At the age of three months, Lee Hoi Chuen, his wife Grace and baby Bruce returned to Hong Kong where Bruce would be raised until the age of 18. Probably because of the long ocean voyage and the change in climates, Bruce was not a strong child in his very early years, a condition that woul...\n\nQ: It can be inferred from the passage that   _  .", "options": ["Bruce didn't have outstanding academic achievements in school", "Master Yip Man offered to teach Bruce Chinese kung fu for free", "Bruce's parents sent him back to San Francisco for better education", "Bruce made a big fortune by participating in boxing competitions"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3418, "question": "I am a professor of sports and exercise so I often deal with nervousness in my research with sports people. Actually, most people experience nervousness at some time or another. If you are feeling anxious, my advice is to first find the cause or causes. Make a list of those things that are making you nervous and work out which ones you can do something about. Focus all of your efforts on managing the causes that you can control. Most people cannot tell the difference between controllable and uncontrollable causes, so things they can't control become a big reason for nervousness. Dealing with this is very important if people want to keep a healthy mind. Simply try to accept the uncontrollable causes of nervousness. You might be worried about the weather on a big day, an accident or an attac...\n\nQ: What is TRUE about nervousness according to the passage?", "options": ["It usually has only one cause.", "It is usually caused by people.", "People can easily manage it.", "Most people suffer from it."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1423, "question": "The Internet has led to a huge increase in credit-card fraud.Your card information can even be on sale on an illegal website.Websites offering cheap goods and services should be regarded with care.Online shoppers who enter their credit-card information may never receive the goods they thought they had bought. The thieves then go shopping with your card number--or sell the information over the Internet.Computer hackers have broken down security system, raising questions about the safety of card holder information. Several months ago, 25,000 customers of a CD universe, an online music retailer , were not lucky.Their names, addresses and credit-card numbers were posted on a Website after the retailer refused to pay $ 157,828 to get back the information.Credit-card firms are now fighting again...\n\nQ: If the passwords of your credit-cards are not properly kept,   _  .", "options": ["the bank and the shop will suffer great losses", "you will not be able to get back your information", "you might suffer great losses", "the bank will answer for your loss"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2962, "question": "Advertisers tend to think big and perhaps this is why they're always getting criticism. Their critics seem to resent(...) them because they have a gift for self-promotion and because they have so much money to throw around. 'It's unjust,' they say, 'that this entirely unproductive industry (if we can call it that) should absorb millions of pounds each year. It only goes to show how much profit the big companies are making. Why don't they stop advertising and reduce the price of their goods? After all, it's the consumer who pays...' The poor old consumer! He'd have to pay a great deal more if advertising didn't create mass markets for products. It is precisely because of the heavy advertising that consumer goods are so cheap. But we get the wrong idea if we think the only purpose of adverti...\n\nQ: What is main idea of this passage?", "options": ["Advertisements.", "Advertisements bring fun to readers.", "Advertisers perform a useful service to communities.", "The costs of advertisements."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3367, "question": "One day, I was studying at home . Suddenly, there was a loud noise. I went out of my house to see what had happened . What I saw made me scared. A building in my neighborhood was on fire. Some people were using water to put out the fire; others were rushing towards the building to help put out the fire. The building had three floors. The fire started on the first floor. Soon, it spread to the second floor. There were some people on the second floor at that time. Their lives were in danger. A few people jumped out of the window. Luckily, they only got small injuries. Those who were still on the second floor were just crying for help. The people outside didn't know how to help the people inside to get out. Firefighters arrived at last. They fought the fire bravely. Water pipes were used and ...\n\nQ: The people who jumped out of the window  _  .", "options": ["were seriously injured", "died", "were taken to the hospital", "got small injuries"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1500, "question": "First Lady Michelle Obama is a big fan of volunteering. Volunteering means working for free to help someone else. Mrs. Obama says volunteering is very important. \"It should be part of everyone's life, \" she says. Many teens agree. They say that helping others feels great and makes a difference. These days, more teens volunteer than work for pay. Teens clean up parks, walk dogs at animal shelters , visit the elderly and more. Some cities ---- including Seatle, Chicago, and Washingtong,D.C. ----require high school students to volunteer. Students must volunteer in order to graduate. The student volunteers learn new skills and help theircommunities . Many parents _ the idea ---- they say volunteering helps teens build job skills. But most teens don't want to be forced to volunteer. They say th...\n\nQ: According to the text, in Chicago,  _  .", "options": ["finding a volunteer job is quite easy", "more people would rather work for pay", "volunteering is a must for high school students", "college students have to volunteer before graduation"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1794, "question": "Have you ever wanted to achieve a goal and ended up doing tons of research on how to achieve the goal? As you learn more and more, it feels like you know less and less because when you learn something new, you find that there is a lot to know about those things. Sometimes, people will get stuck in this needing to gather more and more information. There's nothing wrong with learning a lot, but when you let learning get in the way of doing, you will never get going. When you never get going, you still never start having the things you want. Too much learning can paralyze you in terms of taking action. A better way to go about achieving a goal is to gather some information and immediately start taking action on the information you have gathered. Many times you will feel unprepared, and that's...\n\nQ: The passage implies that the more we learn,  _  .", "options": ["the less we will know", "the more we want to explore", "the more likely we are to succeed", "the better preparations we will make"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 214, "question": "The Mysterious Universe By Ellen Jackson and Nic Bishop How did the universe begin? How big is it? What is dark matter? Cosmologist and expert supernova hunter Alex Filippenko hopes that supernovas can help us answer some of these questions. But first we've got to find them! Join Alex and his team as they go on the hunt with huge telescopes and banks of computers. The Time and Space of Uncle Albert By Russell Stannard What would you say if your uncle asked you whether you would like to go into space? You'd say, \"When do I leave?\", just like the girl in this story. Gedanken is speeding across the universe trying to help her uncle answer some questions, such as \"How big is space?\" and \"Where does gravity come from?\" Along the way she also discovers how to get heavier without getting fat, how...\n\nQ: What do we know about George's Secret Key to the Universe?", "options": ["It is a sad story", "It is about a pet pig", "It is a co-authored book", "It is based on a real life story."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 426, "question": "Do you have a hobby--something you really enjoy doing in your spare time? Have you ever wondered what it would be like if you could spend more time on your hobby and less time at work? Maybe it's not an either/or situation. Perhaps you can do both at the same time. When choosing a career, one of the things you must consider is your interests. Why then do so many people not even think about their hobbies when a hobby is, in fact, an interest? Perhaps it's because even Webster's Dictionary defines a hobby as \"a pursuit (,) outside one's regular occupation \". Maybe this is a rule you should break. After all, no one ever said your hobby had to stay separate from your occupation. In addition people are usually very skilled at their hobbies. The combination of interest and skill is a very compel...\n\nQ: By writing this passage, the writer wants to introduce   _  .", "options": ["how to choose a hobby for your free time", "how to develop your own hobby", "how to treat your job as a hobby", "how to turn a hobby into a career"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2368, "question": "All the oceans of the world will be dead in the future unless action is taken at once. How can this happen? We have already seen that people allow all sorts of waste products to flow into the sea. It is almost impossible to measure how much waste water and industrial waste in our oceans, but we can find out how much oil is poured into them legally and illegally. It is illegal to pour oil into the sea close to the shore, but when a ship is many miles out to sea, there are no such rules. Scientists have different ideas as to the amount of oil putting into the sea, but the lowest figure for oil poured in European waters alone is nearly 200 000 tons every year. Some people say the figure could be ten times as high. It is not only our coasts that suffer from oil pollution. Many shell fish, for ...\n\nQ: According to the passage, which one is TRUE?", "options": ["The amount of oil put into the sea is nearly 2000 000 tons in the globe.", "Every year, the figure for oil poured in the ocean is 1000 000 tons in Europe.", "Some people think the figure for oil poured is estimated too low.", "The highest amount of oil put into the oceans reaches 1000 000 tons in globe."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3149, "question": "Working Wives Last week, we published an article about modern marriage. A recent survey showed that in England 51 percent of married women go out to work . people were asked what they thought of \"working wives\". The results were as follow: Men Women In favor 70% 80% Against 10% 20% Don't know 20% 0% We asked readers to write and tell us their opinions. Here are some of the hundreds of letters we received. I'm a (woman)photographer. I make plenty of money, travel a lot, and meet a lot of people. I enjoy my work, and would hate to stay at home. I would never marry a man who wanted me to give up my work. Ms. Jojo O Leary Hampstead At present there are over 1,000,000 unemployed men in Britain. If a woman gets a job, she puts one more man out of work. Perhaps that man has a wife and twelve chil...\n\nQ: When the bus driver goes to work,   _  .", "options": ["her children take care of themselves", "a nurse looks after her children instead of her", "her husband looks after the children", "she has to have everything ready for the family"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1766, "question": "Dear Cassy, Thanks for reminding me by e-mail that you want to baby-sit our children. In spite of the fact that you are only 15 years old, my wife and I would be willing to consider your application if you can meet a few modest requirements: 1. three letters from teachers who will prove that you have never failed to follow directions perfectly in class and never failed to hand in the homework on time. 2. Submit a note from two doctors which says that you are in perfect health, have never been sick, and will never be sick. 3. Submit a document from your physical education teacher or team coach that proves that you can do each of the following: Run two miles in less than nine minutes, climb an oily rope to a height of twenty feet in thirty seconds while balancing a glass of water on your nos...\n\nQ: From the letter we can know that    _   .", "options": ["Cassy wrote to the Smiths twice", "Cassy loves children very much", "Cassy will be in perfect health", "Cassy does very well in her studies"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1051, "question": "California places limits on water use to deal with the state's four-year drought. Californians are feeling the heat after Governor Jerry Brown announced an order that puts mandatory statewide water cutbacks into effect. California has faced water-use cutbacks in the past. In January 2014, Governor Brown called for residents to curb their water use by 20 percent, but many places around the state failed to meet that goal. This most recent announcement, however, marks the first time in the state's history that mandatory restrictions have been ordered. Most of California's water supply comes from the Sierra Nevada mountain range snowpack. Normally, during the spring and summer, this snow melts and puts new supplies into groundwater. but this past winter, the snowpack reached its lowest point s...\n\nQ: Why will local government remove the 50 million square feet of lawns?", "options": ["To get rid of dry grass", "To decrease the use of water", "To develop the land for water storage", "To grow plants that can block rainstorms"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2802, "question": "Child labor -- the employment of children in industry, often against their will -- has been a problem for many years. Over a hundred years ago, Charles Dickens shocked many of his readers when he described the conditions under which young children worked in British factories. The conditions Dickens described continue almost unchanged today in many parts of the world. The only difference is that today employment of children is confined(limited)to small industries and family businesses, such as hotels, restaurants and particularly farms, rather than to large factories. Girls suffer more from child labor practices than boys. Many of them are forced to start work when they are only ten years old. Although the work they are given to do is often light, it is often harmful to the health. Recently...\n\nQ: Girls' work is   _  .", "options": ["not harmful to the health though it is heavy", "not harmful to the health because it is light", "harmful to the health though it is light.", "harmful to the health because it is heavy"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3336, "question": "Mars is the planet most like Earth.Flying to Mars is a difficult task for humans. There is an experiment with the name \"Mars 500\" in Russia.Six volunteers take part in the experiment.They come from China, Russia, France and Italy.They won't go to outer space.They will stay in small modules on the ground for 520 days.It's just like a real journey In the modules, they will experience a lot: flying to Mars, flying back and working on Mars.During the long \"journey\", the volunteers can only eat space food.They can shower every 10 days.They can call their friends or families.Anyone of them can _ if he doesn't feel well.This experiment helps scientists know how well humans will be on a long journey to Mars. Wangyue, 26, from China, is the youngest of the volunteers.He is a teacher at the China As...\n\nQ: Which of the statement is Not True?", "options": ["The volunteers are not going to move to outer space.", "The volunteers will stay on the Mars for more than 17 months.", "The volunteers can make video calls to their friends and families", "The name of the experiment is \"Mars 500\"."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2629, "question": "Men sometimes say: \"We are better and cleverer than women. Women never invented things. We do.\" It is true that men have invented a lot of useful things: the alphabet, machines, rockets, and guns, too. But scientists and archeologists now agree that women invented one very important thing. It had changed the history. They invented agriculture. Before the invention of agriculture men were hunter. They went out every day. Sometimes they killed animals-sometimes animals killed them. Life was difficult and dangerous. Women had to go out every day, too. They collected roots, fruit and grass. Then, one day, more than 10,000years ago a woman dropped some grass seeds. She dropped them near her home in the Middle East. They grew--and the first wheat was born. The idea grew, too. Women planted roots...\n\nQ: How do you understand agriculture? It means   _  .", "options": ["collecting roots, fruit and grasses", "growing plants and raising animals", "hunting and looking for food", "planting crops"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1667, "question": "Why does a large education nation like China have so few world renowned scientists as the US? Educationists from China and the US try to find out the answer to questions like this at a forum on the basic education strategy. The forum, held recently, was jointly organized by the Education Development Research Center of the Ministry of Education in China and the Postgraduate School of the University of Pennsylvania in the US. It aims to find out similarities and differences that exist between two countries in their educational system. While some educationists in China keep a doubtful eye to the country's educational system in recent years. Their American counterparts give a positive answer to the basic education in China, saying that it is still one of the best in the world. An American educ...\n\nQ: The following statements are true EXCEPT that   _", "options": ["basic education in the US is associated with the government's political interest.", "the forum aims to find out the reason why there few world masters in China.", "all the educationists in China cast doubts in the country's educational system.", "Chinese government's stress on basic education is spoken highly of."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1234, "question": "Joan, super visor of the town's morals recently accused George, a local man, of having a drinking problem because she noticed his car outside the town's only bar.She reasoned, it was a logical assumption .George stared at her for a moment and said nothing.Later that evening, he parked his car in front of her house and left it there all night. Why is it that so many of our logical assumptions are just plain wrong? And why do we want to act as if they must be true? In an age long before the Internet, a young American at a party found himself seated next to the famous Chinese diplomat Wellington Koo.Completely not knowing what to say to someone from such a different culture, this young man turned and asked, \"Likee soupee?\" After all, he assumed, don't all Chinese speak in broken English? Mr.K...\n\nQ: Wellington Koo's experience is mentioned to show   _  .", "options": ["his talent in speaking English", "people's assumption can be false", "the Chinese were looked down on", "his humor in doing with difficult situations"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 625, "question": "British newspapers are among the oldest and most famous in the world. But recently big changes have seen these traditional publications try to fit the modern world. After 221 years, The Times has changed its size to become much smaller. In fact, the paper has cut its size in half from a broadsheet to tabloid . In prefix = st1 /Britainthe newspaper market is divided between the larger broadsheets and the smaller tabloids. These terms refer to the size of the papers' pages but there is also a clear difference in content. Broadsheets such as The Times, the Guardian and Daily Telegraph are serious papers. They cover a broad range of political, economic and international issues. Their stories are also reasonably long and use quite formal language. Tabloids have far more stories about less serio...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements can best describe broadsheets and tabloid?", "options": ["Broadsheets are larger in size while tabloids are smaller.", "Tabloids are less serious than broadsheets.", "Broadsheets contain more news than tabloids.", "They are different in size, content and the style of language."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 374, "question": "My friend Mike was shaking his head in disbelief. \"That young woman who just waited on me,\" he said, pointing to an employee of the fast food restaurant where we were eating, \"had to call someone over to help her count change. The cash register showed her I needed 99 cents, but she couldn't figure out how to count out the coins.\" I understood Mike's concern. What we have done is to create several generations of individuals most of whom have no idea how to reason; how to do simple math; how to do research; or, finally, how to be creative . The reason for this is our overuse of information technology: video games, television, digital watches, calculators, and computers. Information technology feeds us information without requiring us to think about it and let us perform operations without un...\n\nQ: According to the text, Mike worries that   _  .", "options": ["information technology is developing too fast.", "many restaurants do not provide good service", "we are creating people who cannot think for themselves", "modern technology feeds us with too much information"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1781, "question": "Shoplifting is happening in stores or supermarkets throughout the world. However, shoplifting happens more in British stores, according to a recent research, by the UK-based Center for Retail Research. Napoleon once considered prefix = st1 /Britainas \"a nation of shopkeepers\", to which so many people dreamed of traveling. Now it seems it is a nation of shoplifters. According to the research,Britainis the most light-fingered country in Europe, with nearly one in every two cases of shoplifting across the continent taking place in British stores. The report said there were nearly 566,000 reported cases of shoplifting inBritainout of a Europe-wide total of 1.27 million. The next worst countries in Europe,FranceandGermany, came well belowBritainwith only 188,000 and 167,000 cases, respectively....\n\nQ: What's the main idea of this passage?", "options": ["Protecting ourselves is important when shopping.", "Shoplifting is becoming serious, especially in Britain.", "Shoplifting does great harm to people across Europe.", "Europe is suffering many traveling groups of thieves."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1369, "question": "\"Make-A-Wish\" is one of the world's most well-known charities . It makes wishes come true for childrenwho have serious illnesses. It gives them hope and joy and helps them forget about their health problems and have fun. It all started in 1980 in Phoenix, Arizona. Christopher was a 7-year-old boy who was very sick. He always dreamed ofbecoming a police officer. Tommy Austin and Ron Cox, two police officers, made his wish come true. They gaveChristopher a tour of the city in a police helicopter and made a real police uniform for him. There are four kinds of wishes children usually have: I wish to go. Children usually want to travel or go to a concert, a game or a park. I wish to meet. Children sometimes want to meet their favourite actors, singers or players. I wish to be. Some children wis...\n\nQ: \"Make-A-Wish\" is a charity to help   _  .", "options": ["sick children", "serious officers", "famous actors", "popular singers"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1323, "question": "Growing up in one of the poorest, most crime-ridden communities on the south side of Atlanta, US, being raised by a single mother who didn't finish 3rd grade, living each day on food stamps and attending what the media called \"the most dysfunctional public school district,\" not many people expected much of me, so I had to expect something of myself. On my 13th birthday, I bought a poster of Harvard to hang in my room. Being at Harvard became what I dreamt about: I saw myself attending class in Sanders Theater, studying in Widener Library and eating in Annenberg Hall. Even when my electricity was cut off and I woke up at 5:30 a.m. to pitch blackness, I knew that my poster of Harvard was still hanging only two feet away from me. I'd begin my day by asking myself these two questions, \"What do...\n\nQ: How did motivating  himself affect the author?", "options": ["It focused him on improving his application essays.", "It helped him with decision-making and got him to put in extra effort where necessary.", "It allowed him to measure how effectively he was moving towards achieving the goals.", "It helped him better communicate with others in his application for colleges and scholarships."], "answer": 1}]